You can't help but fall.
The Devil's Carnival is a horror, music film directed by Darren Lynn Bousman.
Sinners are invited to a theme park where they endure
the repetition of their transgressions.
What chances do a conniving kleptomaniac, a gullible teenager, and an
obsessed father stand when facing their own moral failings?
Lucifer and his colorful cast of singing carnies invite you to
grab a ticket to The Devil’s Carnival to find out!
John, played by Sean Patrick Flanery.
Ms. Merrywood, played by Briana Evigan.
Tamara, played by Jessica Lowndes.
The Magician, played by Bill Moseley.
Ticket-Keeper, played by Dayton Callie.
God, played by Paul Sorvino.
The Devil's Carnival is a 2012 American musical horror film directed by Darren Lynn Bousman and starring Sean
Patrick Flanery, Briana Evigan, Jessica Lowndes, Paul Sorvino, Emilie Autumn and Terrance Zdunich.
The film marks the second collaboration of Bousman and writer/actor Terrance
Zdunich, their previous work being the musical film Repo!
The Genetic Opera.
The film also brings back several of the cast members of Repo!, such
as Sorvino, Alexa Vega, Bill Moseley and Nivek Ogre.
The Devil's Carnival has Aesop's Fables and other folklore at the core of its
story, with the main characters each representing a fable.
Flanery's character John represents "Grief and His Due", Evigan's character Merrywood represents "The Dog and Its Reflection", and
Lowndes' character Tamara represents "The Scorpion and the Frog", an animal fable that seems to have first emerged in Russia.
The film explores themes of hell, clown, redemption, musical, sin.
The tone is dark.